newtonsoft.com 2019-07-31

# Privacy Policy - Newtonsoft

### Information Collected

You may visit our Site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Our Site does collect information such as domain names, IP address, browser type, operating system, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Newtonsoft for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service and for site trends and statistics. This information does not personally identify you. 

We do not sell, rent, or give your personal information to any third party. And we do not use your information for any purpose outside the scope of communicating with you in the most efficient manner. We may use your personal information to deliver services, such as newsletters, events, training or software, that you request or purchase. We may also use any information you have provided as reasonably necessary to provide customer support to you. 

### Use of Cookies

We may use cookies from time to time. Cookies are small text files a web site can use to recognize a repeat visitor to the web site. We may use cookies for various reasons. If you do not want Newtonsoft to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of this Site, however, your ability to use some of the products and/or services at this Site may be affected. 

### Links to Third Party Sites

At this Site, there may be links to companies with whom we have a relationship. Newtonsoft is not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners. We encourage you to read their privacy statements, as they may differ from ours.
